[{"answer": "The Republican proposal is the worst of all worst.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "How much more money do we want to steal from the American people to fund more government?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "No, you're not wrong, Piers.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Am I wrong?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "This sort of kind of goes into effect over a few days and weeks, right?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "Right, but I think you can blame the president.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "And as -- and as the CEO of the country, who should call the meeting?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "No, and I think it's -- it's incumbent upon the leader to make that happen, not the speaker.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Do you see that happening here?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "If I -- you have somebody -- if I were the CEO of the country, I'd be able to have a meeting when I want to have a meeting, and I'd work it out.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "But the speaker is just as intransigent?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "We're spending $3.8 trillion while we're talking about these cuts.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Is it all just fiddling while Rome burns, Jack?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "It certainly doesn't make the tent bigger, I'll tell you that.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Is this -- is this a problem for the Republicans that their most positive in terms of public opinion politician is already getting snubbed by the party?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's two parts to that question, Piers.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Do you think you can get more done as a team physically together?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Look, she's not going to throw out great performers.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "-- but enjoyed working from home to continue?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "We sure did, Piers.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "We had it all, didn't we?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I don't remember.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Ma'am, were you crying when you were shooting him?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "I don't remember.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Were you crying when you were stabbing him?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Were you crying then?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I don't think she has any chance of being acquitted.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, has she got any chance of getting off this from everything you're hearing?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, it's 3:30 in the morning.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "What does she say to you?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Don't know.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "May I ask was that before or after she had sex with the man in Utah after she killed Travis?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Did you speak to her again where she denied killing him?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "That was it.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "That was it?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "But she never gave any indication that she'd been responsible for the death?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, and I'm not saying that, you know, he deliberately had a spell on her.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "In what way was she addicted, do you think?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, I never saw them together.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Was it, from what you saw of them together -- was it an abusive relationship?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "No, I did not know him to be.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "From what you knew of Travis, was he an abusive character?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I was completely shocked.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "I mean, you must have been shocked, aren't you?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "No, she was completely trustworthy.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Was she somebody you wouldn't completely trust?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, it's much worse than that.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "It's a classic cover your tracks, isn't it?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, it really is getting sinister.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Would somebody risk their job to do that kind of research?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Well, I think there are two things going on.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Am I right to feel disquieted?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Well, I think I may be somebody who believes in the Pope's position more than most Catholics.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What is your honest reaction to it all?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "No, that's the point.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Don't you follow everything?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I don't think she needs an excuse at all.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Is that a good enough excuse?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "You have every right to be offended by it.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Is that acceptable?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I think there are limits to each one of us and our tastes and what we will enjoy.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "No limits?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Isn't that the most beautiful thing in the world?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "It absolutely is.", "docId": "130228pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Does he know what he's doing?", "qSentId": 587}]